There	O
's	O
a	O
concept	O
album	O
by	O
A	B-musicartist
Challenge	I-musicartist
of	I-musicartist
Honour	I-musicartist
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gunter	B-person
Grass	I-person
novel	O
too	O
.	O

Outlook	B-product
does	O
n't	O
even	O
compete	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
users	O
as	O
GMail	B-product
.	O

Psychonauts	B-product
.	O
Realms	B-product
of	I-product
the	I-product
Haunting	I-product
.	O
The	O
2nd	O
Crusader	B-product
game	O
.	O
Beyond	B-product
Good	I-product
and	I-product
Evil	I-product
as	O
said	O
before	O
.	O
Stonekeep	B-product
.	O
Space	B-product
Rogue	I-product
.	O
Wrath	B-product
of	I-product
Denethenor	I-product
.	O

they	O
're	O
just	O
bundling	O
Thunderbird	B-product
/	O
Lightning	B-product
into	O
OpenOffice	B-product
.	O

you	O
can	O
find	O
more	O
information	O
about	O
nevada	B-geo-loc
football	O
here	O
:	O

If	O
you	O
minimized	O
a	O
program	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
use	O
Option-Tab	O
to	O
scroll	O
over	O
programs	O
,	O
once	O
you	O
selected	O
the	O
program	O
you	O
wanted	O
to	O
activate	O
,	O
the	O
windows	O
still	O
a	O
no-show	O

Nader	B-person
is	O
quoting	O
US	B-geo-loc
congressman	O
John	B-person
Olver	I-person
's	O
response	O
to	O
the	O
councils	O
of	O
13	O
towns	O
in	O
his	O
district	O
(	O
Massachusetts	B-geo-loc
'	O
first	O
)	O
that	O
have	O
called	O
for	O
impeachment	O
this	O
year	O
.	O

but	O
we	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
if	O
S	O
(	O
action	O
)	O
~	O
E	O
(	O
energy	O
)	O
x	O
t	O
(	O
time	O
)	O
was	O
comparable	O
to	O
Planck	B-person
's	O
constant	O
(	O
10^-39	O
)	O

Justice	O
.	O

There	O
are	O
closed	O
source	O
products	O
which	O
work	O
happily	O
with	O
Exchange	B-product
.	O

This	O
Unreal	B-product
Tournament	I-product
3	I-product
demo	O
patch	O
is	O
the	O
fix	O
for	O
the	O
game	O
not	O
starting	O
up	O
on	O
some	O
systems	O

gaped	O
tooth	O
moron	O
is	O
Rice	B-person

So	O
he	O
does	O
n't	O
like	O
C	B-other
,	O
but	O
he	O
's	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
options	O
that	O
truly	O
fill	O
C	B-other
's	O
niche	O
.	O

C	B-other
is	O
fast	O
.	O

C	B-other
binaries	O
are	O
small	O
and	O
compact	O
.	O

Ever	O
since	O
the	O
update	O
,	O
the	O
filter	O
does	O
n't	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
working	O
properly	O
.	O

HTTP	O
/	O
JSON	O
layer	O
aside	O
,	O
how	O
does	O
this	O
differ	O

Al-Qaeda	B-other
In	O
Iraq	B-geo-loc
Reported	O
Stronger	O
Than	O
Ever	O

Al-Qaeda	B-other
In	O
Iraq	B-geo-loc
Reported	O
Crippled	O

C	B-other
is	O
easy	O
.	O

And	O
what	O
's	O
Dick	B-person
Cheney	I-person
doing	O
on	O
Air	B-other
Force	I-other
One	I-other
?	O

It	O
is	O
worrisome	O
and	O
undermines	O
progress	O
towards	O
a	O
drug-free	O
South	B-geo-loc
East	I-geo-loc
Asia	I-geo-loc
,	O
according	O
to	O
UNDOC	B-other
.	O

'	O
Fiat	O
Empire	O
'	O
:	O

Because	O
I	O
can	O
implement	O
almost	O
any	O
functionality	O
in	O
C	B-other
that	O
those	O
language	O
have	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'm	O
willing	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
on	O
Syntactic	O
sugar	O
.	O

Sony	B-company
is	O
so	O
successful	O
today	O
*because*	O
it	O
got	O
into	O
content	O
creation	O
and	O
media	O
IP	O
.	O

It	O
does	O
n't	O
exist	O
until	O
they	O
release	O
it	O
for	O
PC	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O

EDIT	O
:	O
Off	O
subject	O
but	O
does	O
anyone	O
else	O
think	O
that	O
when	O
Rush	B-person
talks	O
he	O
sounds	O
like	O
he	O
's	O
constantly	O
burping	O
up	O
a	O
meatloaf	O
and	O
is	O
moments	O
away	O
from	O
a	O
vomit	O
?	O

Osama	B-person
Bin	I-person
laden	I-person
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O

Joe	B-person
the	I-person
Asshole	I-person
!	O

Last	O
year	O
I	O
*drove*	O
to	O
the	O
Mossman	B-person
to	O
see	O
the	O
city	O
.	O

I	O
know	O
I	O
'm	O
being	O
pedantic	O
,	O
but	O
just	O
FYI	O
,	O
the	O
proper	O
abbreviation	O
for	O
PCI	B-other
Express	I-other
is	O
PCIe	B-other
.	O

And	O
then	O
you	O
said	O
the	O
President	O
is	O
to	O
an	O
extent	O
a	O
PR	O
front	O
man	O
.	O

In	O
1943	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
occupying	O
nazis	B-other
enforced	O
the	O
yellow	O
star	O
for	O
jews	O
in	O
Europe	B-geo-loc
,	O
the	O
king	B-person
of	I-person
denmark	I-person
started	O
displaying	O
one	O
.	O

there	O
where	O
only	O
around	O
2000	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
resistance	O
movement	O
against	O
the	O
nazis	B-other
,	O
while	O
there	O
where	O
more	O
than	O
30.000	O
that	O
joined	O
the	O
nazis	B-other
as	O
fighting	O
soldiers	O
.	O

Well	O
you	O
already	O
have	O
a	O
Reddit	B-company
account	O
.	O

There	O
are	O
no	O
peace	O
deals	O
that	O
make	O
sense	O
for	O
the	O
israelis	B-other
.	O

The	O
Atom	B-product
330	I-product
is	O
a	O
dual	O
core	O
1.6GHz	O
chip	O
aimed	O
at	O
desktop	O
use	O
.	O

It	O
's	O
not	O
equivalent	O
to	O
the	O
N270	B-product
used	O
in	O
the	O
eee	B-product
.	O

I	O
figured	O
that	O
was	O
something	O
that	O
Reddit	B-company
did	O
.	O

Steam	B-company
deal	O
today	O
has	O
Morrowind	B-product
and	O
Oblivion	B-product
67	O
%	O
off	O
.	O

Super	B-product
Street	I-product
Fighter	I-product
2	I-product

MGS3	B-product
is	O
getting	O
a	O
3ds	B-product
remake	O
.	O

Thank	O
you	O
Captain	B-person
Obvious	I-person
.	O

Also	O
why	O
Brink	B-product
does	O
n't	O
seem	O
to	O
control	O
right	O
for	O
me	O
.	O

Regulus	B-person
and	O
Kreachers	B-person
story	O
.	O

I	O
'm	O
converting	O
to	O
Islam	O
ASAP	O
.	O

I	O
did	O
n't	O
think	O
to	O
Google+	B-person
it	O
.	O

For	O
the	O
Obamacrats	O
,	O
WHATEVER	O
the	O
President	B-person
stands	O
for	O
is	O
what	O
THEY	O
stand	O
for	O
(	O
and	O
excuse	O
and	O
rationalize	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
by	O
some	O
miracle	O
Obama	B-person
were	O
to	O
dramatically	O
reverse	O
course	O
and	O
start	O
fiercely	O
and	O
consistently	O
advocating	O
progressive	O
solutions	O
so	O
would	O
they	O
.	O

down	O
,	O
R	O
,	O
up	O
,	O
L	O
,	O
Y	O
,	O
B	O

The	O
reasons	O
for	O
having	O
Shift	O
=	O
run	O
and	O
Control	O
=	O
crouch	O
is	O
because	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
do	O
both	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
so	O
it	O
makes	O
sense	O
to	O
choose	O
which	O
one	O
with	O
one	O
finger	O
.	O

Nikon	B-product
D5100	I-product
with	O
Nikkor	B-product
18-55mm	I-product
lens	O
.	O

